{
    "subject": "Trip_Hawkins",
    "predicate": "isKnownFor",
    "object": "Electronic_Arts",
    "human_readable": "Trip Hawkins is known for Electronic Arts.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.759354829788208,
            "question": "Is Trip Hawkins known for a specific company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7554187774658203,
            "question": "What is Electronic Arts primarily known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.54813551902771,
            "question": "Who established Electronic Arts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5366660952568054,
            "question": "What company is Trip Hawkins associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4753551185131073,
            "question": "Who founded Electronic Arts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4148370623588562,
            "question": "What industry is Electronic Arts involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04045569896697998,
            "question": "Name a prominent figure in the video game industry."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03656915947794914,
            "question": "Can you name a famous video game developer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.015601357445120811,
            "question": "Which company created popular video games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.014160951599478722,
            "question": "What company revolutionized the gaming industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Trip Hawkins is known for Electronic Arts.",
            "html": "yago_31471_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which company created popular video games?",
            "html": "yago_31471_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a famous video game developer?",
            "html": "yago_31471_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a prominent figure in the video game industry.",
            "html": "yago_31471_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31471_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31471_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31471_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31471_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31471_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31471_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31471_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31471_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31471_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31471_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Trip Hawkins is known for Electronic Arts\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently mention that Trip Hawkins founded or was involved with Electronic Arts, The 3DO Company, and other gaming-related companies. This suggests a strong association between Trip Hawkins and Electronic Arts."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that William \"Trip\" Hawkins founded and was the founder of Electronic Arts (EA), making it evident that he is indeed known for Electronic Arts."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}